Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Duplicate copies, first set, 1914-2008
  - Vol. LXIV, no. 20. Courses of instruction, Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1967-1968, September 6, 1967 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. LXV, no. 18. Courses of instruction, Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1969, September 2, 1968 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. LXVI, no. 12. Courses of instruction, 1969-1970, August 15, 1969 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXVII, no. 17. Courses of instruction, 1970-1971, August 31, 1970 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXVIII, no. 4. Courses of instruction, 1971-1972, April 16, 1971 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXIX, no. 4. Courses of instruction, 1972-1973, April 28, 1972 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXX, no. 7. Courses of instruction, 1973-1974, June 29, 1973 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXXI, no. 3. Courses of instruction, 1974-1975, April 30, 1974 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXXI, no. 7. Rules relating to College studies, general academic rules, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1974-1975, June 28, 1974 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. LXXII, no. 4. Courses of instruction, 1975-1976, August 1, 1975 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXXIII. Rules relating to College studies, general academic rules, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1976-1977 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. LXXIV Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1978-1979 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. LXXVI, Higher degrees in biology, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, July 1979 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1979-1980 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 2, no. 6. Courses of instruction, 1980-1981, September 10, 1980 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. LXXIX. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1980-1981, July 2, 1982 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. 3, no. 6. Courses of instruction, 1981-1982, September 8, 1981 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 4, no. 6. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, 1982-1983, August 1982 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1982-1983 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. 5, no. 6. Courses of instruction, 1983-1984, August 10, 1983 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 5, no. 2. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences general announcement, 1983-1984, July 2, 1983 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. 6, no. 5. Courses of instruction, 1984-1985, August 6, 1984 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 7, no. 5. Courses of instruction, 1985-1986, August 6, 1985 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1986-1987 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. 9, no. 5. Courses of instruction, 1987-1988, August 7, 1987 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 9, no. 3. Harvard University Extension School course catalog, 1987-1988, July 9, 1987 (HU 75.25 B Box 12)
  - Vol. 10, no. 5, Courses of instruction, 1988-1989, August 18, 1988 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. 11, no. 5, Courses of instruction, 1989-1990, August 21, 1989 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - General catalogue, 1989-1990 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - General catalogue, 1990-1991 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Courses of instruction, 1990-1991 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Vol. 12, no. 5, Courses of instruction, 1990-1991, August 19, 1990 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. 13, no. 5, Courses of instruction, 1991-1992, August 10, 1991 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Vol. 14. No. 5. Courses of instruction, 1992-1993, August 10, 1992 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - General catalogue, 1992-1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1992-1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
  - Vol. 15, no. 5. Handbook for students, Harvard College, 1993-1994, August 21, 1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 3)
  - Vol. 15, no. 5. Handbook for students, Harvard College, 1993-1994, August 21, 1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 3)
  - Extension School, 1993-1994 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Vol. 15, no. 5. Information for instructors, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1993-1994, August 21, 1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 3)
  - Vol. 15, no. 5. Courses of instruction, 1993-1994, August 10, 1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 2)
  - Vol. 15, no. 7. Harvard and Radcliffe, 1993-1994, August 20, 1993 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
  - Vol. 15 no. 12. Harvard University Summer School, 1994, February 1, 1994 (HU 75.25 B Box 3)
  - Vol. 16, no. 3. Harvard University Extension School, 1994-1995, July 9, 1994 (HU 75.25 B Box 3)
  - Vol. 16, no. 5, Courses of instruction, 1994-1995, August 10, 1994 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - Harvard and Radcliffe, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 B Box #)
  - Summer School, 1995 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Vol. 17, no. 5. Courses of instruction, 1995-1996, August 10, 1995 (HU 75.25 B Box 1)
  - GSAS student handbook, 1995-1996 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Divinity School, 1995-1996 (2 copies) (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Extension School, 1995-1996 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - JFK School catalogue, 1995-1996 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Summer School, 1996 (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Extension School, 1996-1997 (2 copies) (HU 75.25 B Box 13)
  - Courses of instruction, 1996-1997 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - GSAS student handbook, 1996-1997 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Information for instructors, 1996-1997 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 1996-1997 (3 copies) (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Summer School, 1997 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - GSAS student handbook, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Information for instructors, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Extension School, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Courses of instruction, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, 1997-1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 14)
  - Harvard University Extension School, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Harvard Summer School, 1998 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Courses of Instruction, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Handbook, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Information for Faculty offering instruction in Arts and Sciences, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, 1998-1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Harvard Summer School, 1999 (HU 75.25 B Box 4)
  - Harvard Extension School, 1999-2000 (HU 75.25 B Box 5)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2000 (HU 75.25 B Box 5)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handbook, 1999-2000 (HU 75.25 B Box 5)
  - Handbook for Students, 1999-2000 (HU 75.25 B Box 5)
  - Courses of Instruction, 1999-2000 (HU 75.25 B Box 5)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - Information for Faculty offering instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handbook, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - Harvard Extension School, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 B Box 6)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 2001-2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 7)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2001-2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 7)
  - Information for Faculty offering instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2001-2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 7)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handbook, 2001-2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 7)
  - Harvard University Extension School Course Catalogue, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 B Box 8)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 8)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2002 (HU 75.25 B Box 8)
  - Information for Faculty Offering Instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 B Box 8)
  - Handbook for students, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 B Box 8)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 B Box 9)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 B Box 9)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handbook, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 B Box 9)
  - Information for Faculty Offering Instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 B Box 9)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 B Box 10)
  - Handbook for students, fields of concentration, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 B Box 10)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handbook, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 B Box 10)
  - Information for Faculty Offering Instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 B Box 10)
  - Harvard University Summer School, 2005 (HU 75.25 B Box 10)
  - Information for Faculty Offering Instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 B Box 11)
  - Handbook for Students, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 B Box 11)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 B Box 11)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 B Box 11)
  - Harvard University Extension School course catalog, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
  - Harvard University Extension School course catalog, 2006-2007 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2007 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
  - Harvard University Extension School, 2008-2009 (HU 75.25 B Box 15)
- Duplicate copies, second set, 1990-2008
  - Harvard University Extension School Course Catalogue, 1990-1991 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard Summer School, 1990 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard University Extension School Course Catalogue, 1991-92 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard Summer School, 1991 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Courses of instruction, 1992-1993 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard University Extension School Course Catalogue, 1992-93 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard University Extension School Course Catalogue, 1993-94 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard Summer School, 1994 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, 1995-1996 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Student Handbook, The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1996-1997 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2000-2001 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Courses of instruction, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Extension School, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Handbook for students, 2002-2003The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: handbook, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Information for faculty offering instruction in arts and sciences, 2002-2003 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2003 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Courses of instruction, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Handbook for students, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: handbook, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Information for faculty offering instruction in arts and sciences, 2003-2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 1)
  - Courses of instruction, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Handbook for students, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: handbook, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Information for faculty offering instruction in arts and sciences, 2004-2005 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Courses of Instruction, Supplement, Spring 2004 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Handbook for Students, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 2)
  - Information for Faculty Offering Instruction in Arts and Sciences, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Handbook, The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2005-2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Handbook, The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2006-2007 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Harvard Summer School, 2006 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2007-2008 (HU 75.25 C Box 3)
  - Courses of Instruction, 2008-2009 (HU 75.25 C Box 4)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Handbook for Students, 2008-2009 (HU 75.25 C Box 4)
  - Harvard University Extension School, 2008-2009 (HU 75.25 C Box 4)